♪
Happy New Year everyone! My name is Haru Yamashita.
I'm back home right now, and I'm going to a 20-year-old gathering in my hometown.
I had my hair done this morning,
Now, I'm going to change into a furisode.
Please look forward to seeing how it will turn out.
It's early in the morning, so it's all in my hair.
I decided on a lot of furisodes without even looking at them, so for the first time, I'm going to wear a furisode now,
So, for the first time, I'm going to meet my furisode.
But I'm so happy with my hair, it looks so cute like this.
Well, I'm off now.
Yes, I've finished changing into my furisode. It looks like this.
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da. The obi is beautiful, too.
Yes, the 20-year-old gathering has just finished, and I've come to Sokoname to have fun.
When I say Aichi, I mean Sokoname. Please come to Sokoname.
Now, let's proceed.
Here is a pottery.
This place is famous for pottery.
Keep on walking.
What are your memories of the coming-of-age ceremony?
I was so happy to meet so many children.
Oh, look at this. There are a lot of teapot lids,
Hearts.
They are hearts.
It's so cute.
As pottery is famous here, it looks like a pottery town.
Here we go. It looks like this.
It's amazing.
Now, I'm going to take the shortcut to the pottery walking path, Dojikanzaka.
Oh, wow. Look at this.
Look at this! Look at this.
Amazing. What kind of house is this?
Fifth grader.
Minami Onizaki.
Isn't that Minami Onizaki?
That's amazing. Is she baking this?
This is pottery, isn't it?
She is baking. I'm baking.
It's amazing. I also went to a pottery class with Mr. Kappa,
I would like to do my best in making things so that one day I can be in the same position as you.
Yes, I will do my best.
Tokume's side trip. I am going to meet Tokumusume.
She is very big.
Oh, here she is.
Here. She's looking back.
Look at her.
Ta-da-da-da-da-da.
It's a big Tokumei.
Here, a cat. A small cat.
You can get to know Tokumei like this.
Tokumusume.
If you meet a Tokumusume, please say hello.
Yes, we have come to Tokumoso City, which is filled with the charms of Aichi Prefecture.
How was it?
I often visit Tokumusume, but it was my first time to come to the pottery walkway, so I was very happy.
It is a very peaceful and wonderful place where I met the big Tokumusume and many other potters.
It is a wonderful place that we can do together in Aichi Prefecture, so please come.
I was an adult.
Please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel.
This is Haruka Yamashita.